(+57) 300-782-1311 oquendojair10@gmail.com LinkedIn I Portafolio

Frontend Developer with +4 years of experience developing Frontend Javascript applications with React.js, Next.js Framework, Redux.js, TailwindCSS, SASS or Bootstrap and Backend with Node.js, express. js and MongoDB, I have great capacity for solving problems related to web, I have developed E-Commerce with payment gateway integration, Landing page, finally I have deployed applications on Vercel, Heroku and AWS platforms, blockchain with Ethers.js, Smart Contracts, Solidity or Binance API and virtual environments with Three.js integrated with blockchain networks

EXPERIENCE

BancaCrypto (bancacrypto.money) Medellín, Antioquia, Freelancer, Frontend — April, 2021-Present
Front-end Blockchain Developer, Support in project management and analysis of requirements for Web3 and Blockchain applications, integration and implementation with web3.js, ethers.js, MetaMask, Samart Contract or Solidity.

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TailwindCSS, Vercel, Solidity, Ethers.js Web3.js, Remix, Smart Contracts

<u>DrakeTech (https://www.draketch.ca)</u> Ontario, Canadá, **Forntend** — September, 2021-October, 2022

Front-end developer, web application layout with Ant Design and Bootstrap, integration with APIs and implementation with React and Redux, support in project management and requirements analysis for software implementation.

Technologies: React.js, Redux,js, Javascript, JSON, JWT, Web API Ant Design, Bootstrap, Git, Git flow

<u>Startups Lab - Agencia (startupslabagencia.co)</u>, Frontend — August, 2019-Septiembre, 2021

Frontend developer, web page and web application designer and integration of APIs with the Frontend.

- Reduce web site delivery time to the customer by 80% thanks to Vercel
- Reduce layout time by 40% with Tailwind CSS
- Increased development efficiency by 70% thanks to Git flow

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Vercel

PROJECTS

Paytoshi Commerce - https://paytoshi-commerce.vercel.app/ - November, 2022

Test e-commerce to accept payments with cryptocurrencies, integrating the Payotshi payment processor.

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, express.js, MongoDB, Vercel, Paytoshi, ethers.js

Banca Crypto- https://bancacrypto.money - February, 2021

Investments in the cryptocurrency and traditional markets

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, express.js, MongoDB, Vercel, Paytoshi

BMC Quant - BMC (bybmc.co) - Abril, 2020

financial courses platform.

Sales of courses to customers were optimized by 90%.

Technologies: Next.js React.js, Node.js, express.js, TailwindCSS, AWS S3, Vercel

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Javascript, CSS, SASS, HTML

Frameworks and Tools: Advanced: React, Next.js, Vercel, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, JSON, Web API, Intermediate: Node.js. Git, Gitflow, MongoDB, express.js, AWS, Redux.js, JWT, SASS, Basic: Angular 2+, GraphQL, Typescript, Docker, Python **Languages:** Español, Intermediate English;

EDUCATION

Graphic Design, *January, 2017 - November, 2018* Instituto Tecnológico San Agustín, Montería - Córdoba

Computer Engineer *July, 2011 -July, 2014* Universidad Pontificia Bolivariana, Montería - Córdoba